<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<odoo>

    <!-- === Services Page === -->
    <template name="100% Quality Code" id="website.qua-cod" page="True">
        <t t-call="website.layout">

            <div class="oe_structure"/>



            <section class="open-erp-custamization odoo java text-center  ">
                <h3>
                    <span class="f-nrslight text-center grey ">
                        <span class="orange f-nrssemibld">  100%   </span> Quality Code
                        <div class="clear"></div>
                    </span>
                </h3>
                <div class="down-arrow"></div>

            </section>
            <section class="inner-page">
                <div class="wrapper">
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col8 left-section">
                            <h1 class="f-nrsthin grey">100% Quality Code</h1>

                            <p>Anyone in the world can learn to write a computer program. We believe coding is an

                                art unto itself. We are passionate and proud of writing the best quality code whether

                                it's a mobile application development, web application development, big data

                                analytics, or internet of things.</p>

                            <p>We have implemented some of the best practices to make sure source code quality

                                is maintained across the team. Such practices include:</p>
                            <br></br>

                            <h4 class="f-nrssemibld orange">Software’s test automatization</h4><br></br>

                            <p>Here in Treming, we are concious that a very important base to develope high quality software is “the testing”.
                                For that reason, we have developed an automatized metodology which allow us to do faster and more efficient this
                                task. Also, this process includes to make stress, regretation and concurrence testing of the user.</p>
                            <br></br>




                            <h4 class="f-nrssemibld orange">Peer Code Review</h4><br></br>

                            <p>At the end of the day every developer reviews each team member's code and gives

                                suggestions. Any changes suggested in peer review are bound to be fixed unless the

                                original programmer was able to satisfy their peers as to why it is done a specific

                                way.</p>
                            <br></br>
                            <h4 class="f-nrssemibld orange">Manager Code Review</h4><br></br>

                            <p>Randomly, the code committed to the GIT repository will be reviewed by a Project

                                Manager, Team Leader, Project Lead, or the CTO. All software developers

                                working with Treming are given clear instructions on the Do's and Don'ts.</p>
                            <br></br>
                            <h4 class="f-nrssemibld orange">GIT Restrictions</h4><br></br>

                            <p>We have lexical analyzers implemented on the GIT level so that software developers

                                cannot check in a poor quality code. Such GIT requests will trigger an email to the Project Lead.</p>

                            <p>While all of these quality assurance checks are in place, we keep our software

                                developers happy and effective by encouraging their passion for writing beautiful

                                code rather than it being a chore.</p>
                            <br></br>
                        </div>
                        <div class="col4 last  right-section">
                            <span class="stripe"></span>
                            <h3>Related Topics</h3>
                            <ul>

                                <li><a href="/page/use-cen-des">User centered design </a></li>
                                <li><a href="/page/out">Projects in more than 12 countries</a> </li>

                                <li><a href="/page/open"> Love Technology </a></li>
                                <li><a href="/page/cost-eff">Cost efficiency</a> </li>
                                <li><a href="/page/cod-lib">Code library</a></li>
                                <li><a href="/page/hir"> We Hire The Best People</a></li>
                                <li><a href="/page/cust-par">Customers = Partners</a></li>

                            </ul>

                        </div>
                        <div class="clear"></div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </section>

            <t t-call="website.contactus_custom_template"/>
            <div class="oe_structure"/>
        </t>
    </template>

</odoo>