<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<odoo>

    <!-- === Services Page === -->
    <template name="ODOO" id="website.odoo-custom" page="True">
        <t t-call="website.layout">

            <div class="oe_structure"/>



            <section class="open-erp-custamization odoo java text-center  ">
                <h3>
                    <span class="f-nrslight text-center grey ">
                        Odoo <span class="orange f-nrssemibld"> Customization </span>
                        <div class="clear"></div>
                    </span>
                </h3>
                <div class="down-arrow"></div>

            </section>

            <section class="inner-page">
                <div class="wrapper">
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col8 left-section">
                            <h2>Odoo Customization</h2>
                            <p>Odoo(Previously OpenERP) - an open source suite of ERP business application is one of the most used
                                open source ERP solutions in the world today. Owing to its flexibility, ease of learning and customizability,
                                Odoo has grown to occupy a top position among the list of preferred open source ERP solutions in a variety of
                                verticals and domains.
                                One of the main advantages with using open source ERP solutions is that you get to have your solution customized
                                to fit your business flow and to suit your established processes and models. The idea would be to streamline, improve
                                and increase productivity from the existing processes rather than delve into the ardent task of introducing an
                                all-new system to serve the purpose of living with a proprietary solution. We do all sorts of Odoo customization.
                                Odoo is based on the open source AGPL v3 license as from version 6.0 and has a dedicated community working around
                                scaling the system to introduce features/integrations/modules. All modules are necessarily licensed under the AGPL,
                                while there are provisions to build private modules on Odoo Enterprise version for your internal needs. Odoo is built
                                on Python with database in PostgreSQL.</p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="col4 last  right-section">
                            <span class="stripe"></span>
                            <h3>Related Topics</h3>

                            <ul>

                                <li><a href="/page/odoo-10">Odoo Version 10</a></li>
                                <li><a href="/page/odoo-app-dev">Odoo Development </a> </li>
                                <li><a href="/page/odoo-mod">Odoo Modules</a></li>
                                <li><a href="/page/odoo-video">Odoo Video Gallery</a></li>
                                <li><a href="/page/odoo-com-vs-ent">Odoo Community Vs Enterprise</a></li>
                                <li><a  href="/page/odoo-sus-sto">Odoo Success Stories</a></li>

                                <li><a  href="/page/odoo-cont">Odoo Contributions</a></li>
                                <li><a  href="/page/odoo-dat-mig">Odoo Data Migration</a></li>
                                <li><a  href="/page/odoo-whi-pap">Odoo White Papers </a></li>


                            </ul></div>
                    </div>

                </div>
            </section>
            <section class="content-caption2 padding-sm bg-lgtgrey">
                <div class="content-wrapper">
                    <h2><span class="thick bg-lgtgrey grey">Why <span class="bold">Treming?</span></span></h2>
                    <p class="content">Treming has a proven track record of having provided customized solutions based on Odoo for a number of verticals. The main advantage of Odoo being that it is modular which enables you to install only the desired modules for your specific need. Be it a single module or more that you need to customize or fine-tune to be used in your organization, Treming provides dedicated service on projects of any size. We also specialize on introducing newer modules to serve the user community and integrations with other popular solutions. Our Odoo customization is done by our team of experts.</p>
                </div>
            </section>

            <t t-call="website.contactus_custom_template"/>
            <div class="oe_structure"/>
        </t>
    </template>

</odoo>