<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<odoo>

    <!-- === Services Page === -->
    <template name="ODOO" id="website.odoo-com-vs-ent" page="True">
        <t t-call="website.layout">

            <div class="oe_structure"/>



            <section class="open-erp-custamization odoo java text-center  ">
                <h3>
                    <span class="f-nrslight text-center grey ">
                        <span class="orange f-nrssemibld">Odoo </span>   Community Vs Enterprise
                        <div class="clear"></div>
                    </span>
                </h3>
                <div class="down-arrow"></div>

            </section>




            <section class="inner-page">
                <div class="wrapper">
                    <div class="row">
                        <div class="col8 left-section">

                            <h1 class="f-nrsthin grey">Odoo Community Vs Enterprise</h1><br></br>
                            <p>
                            Starting with Odoo version 9.0, there are two offerings, namely Community and
                            Enterprise. We get a lot of questions regarding the differences between Odoo

                            Enterprise and Odoo Community from our partners, customers and prospective

                            customers.</p><p>

                            Odoo Community version is the base of everything. With every version, changes will

                            be tested and improved upon in the Community version and later pushed to the

                            Enterprise version. Odoo Community version is very important and it’s the

                            backbone of Odoo as explained by CEO of Odoo Fabien Pinckaers.</p>

                            <p class="darkgrey bold">The main differences when it comes to Odoo 9.0 Enterprise are:</p><br></br>

                            <h4 class="f-nrsthin orange bold">Improved User Interface</h4>
                            <p>
                                It’s not an understatement to say that Odoo 9.0 Enterprise has one of the best user

                                interfaces. This makes it stand out from SAP, Netsuite, Microsoft Dynamics, etc. The

                                fully responsive material design using Google material design guidelines is a

                                pleasure to work with. It gives a feeling of mobile phone apps when it comes to

                                usability of modules.</p><br></br>

                            <h4 class="f-nrsthin orange  bold">Improved Accounting</h4>
                            <p>
                                We always hear questions from US customers regarding the PDF reports and the

                                lack of ability to view drilled down accounting reports like P&amp;L statements. Odoo

                                listened to what the customer’s expectations are and executed it in a beautiful way.

                                It’s easy to generate reports, customize templates, and much more.
                            </p><br></br>
                            <h4 class="f-nrsthin orange bold">Paid Licenses</h4>
                            <p>
                                For customers moving from

                                previous versions of Odoo to Odoo 9 Enterprise, Odoo will provide a free core

                                database migration. Treming, being an Odoo Ready Partner, will work with Odoo to

                                make the up gradation smooth and easy. Any custom modules that already exist will

                                be migrated by the Treming Odoo team for a fixed cost after estimation. As a Ready Partner we can procure Odoo licenses for our customers for the

                                best market rates.</p>


                            <br></br>
                        </div>
                        <div class="col4 last  right-section">
                            <span class="stripe"></span>
                            <h3>Related Topics</h3>

                            <ul>
                                <li><a href="/page/odoo-10">Odoo Version 10</a></li>
                                <li><a href="/page/odoo-app-dev"> Odoo Development </a> </li>
                                <li><a href="/page/odoo-mod">Odoo Modules</a></li>
                                <li><a href="/page/odoo-video">Odoo Video Gallery</a></li>
                                
                                <li><a  href="/page/odoo-sus-sto">Odoo Success Stories</a></li>
                                <li><a  href="/page/odoo-custom">Odoo Customization</a></li>
                                <li><a  href="/page/odoo-cont">Odoo Contributions</a></li>
                                <li><a  href="/page/odoo-dat-mig">Odoo Data Migration</a></li>
                                <li><a  href="/page/odoo-whi-pap">Odoo White Papers </a></li>



                            </ul>
                        </div>

                        <div class="clear"></div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </section>

            <t t-call="website.contactus_custom_template"/>
            <div class="oe_structure"/>
        </t>
    </template>

</odoo>